ILGWU. Publications 5780 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Banquet Tendered by the GEB to the Delegates, 1937 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- Commemorating 25th Anniversary of Justice, 1944 (Box 65, Folder 14)
- Minutes of Meeting Held Between the Representatives of the Dress and Waist Manufacturers' Associations and the ILGWU, 1912-1913 (Box 65, Folder 15)
- ILGWU Publications (Box 65, Folder 16)
- Publicity Guide (Box 65, Folder 17)
- ILGWU Song Book, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 18)
- Report: Survey of Members Local 23-25, ILGWU, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 19)
- Trouble on Fashion Avenue (Box 65, Folder 20)
- Twenty-Fifth Anniversary of the Presidency of Dubinsky, 1957 (Box 65, Folder 21)
- "With These Hands" Script (Box 65, Folder 22)
- Working Cards (Box 65, Folder 23)
- The Memoirs of a Cloakmaker, 1883-1910 (Box 65, Folder 24)
- The Trouble with Operator's Local One (Box 65, Folder 25)
- Cartoons from the 1950s in the ILGWU Justice, 1959 (Box 65, Folder 26)
- Report of Educational Department, ILGWU, 1944-1946 (Box 65, Folder 27)
- Student Magazine 1987/1988 (Box 65, Folder 28)
- Student Magazine Vol.I, No.1, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 28)
- Student Magazine Vol.I, No.2, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 28)
- …And the Pursuit of Happiness, 1947 (Box 65, Folder 29)
- Report of the Educational Department, ILGWU, 1951 (Box 65, Folder 30)
- Citizen of the Union: The Union (Box 65, Folder 31)
- Equal Opportunity Union Made (Box 65, Folder 32)
- Growing Up: 21 Years of Education with the ILGWU, 1938 (Box 65, Folder 33)
- Let's Sing! (Box 65, Folder 34)
- Report to the Education Committee of the General Executive Board, ILGWU, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 35)
- Report to the Education Committee of the General Executive Board, ILGWU, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 36)
- Report to the Education Committee of the General Executive Board, ILGWU, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 37)
- Educational Report to General Executive Board (Box 65, Folder 38)
- Report to the Education Committee of the General Executive Board, ILGWU (Box 65, Folder 39)
- Report to the Education Committee of the General Executive Board, ILGWU, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 40)
- Report to the Education Committee of the General Executive Board, ILGWU, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 41)
- Testimonial Dinner in Honor of David Gingold, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 42)
- Vade Mecum, 1946 (Box 65, Folder 43)
- Information Bulletin, 1943 (Box 65, Folder 44)
- Collective Agreement: Industrial Council of Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers Inc. and Designers' Guild of Ladies' Apparel, Local 30, ILGWU, 1952 (Box 65, Folder 45)
- Constitution of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 46)
- Thirty Years of Amalgamated Cooperative Housing 1927-1957, 1958 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Golden Jubilee Journal and Kazan Memorial, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- The Story of the ILGWU Cooperative Houses (Box 66, Folder 3)
- United Housing Foundation: Twenty Years of Accomplishment (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Penn South Twenty-Fifth Anniversary Journal: A Silver Lining in Chelsea, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Highlights in the History of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Profile of a Union, 1958 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Panorama, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Cultural Activities, 1940 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Due Book, 1915 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- To Promote the General Welfare: The Story of the Amalgamated, 1950 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Fiftieth Anniversary Convention: Resolutions, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- Your Dues: Build the Union (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Report and Audited Financial Statements of the General Office, 1957 (Box 66, Folder 14)
- 28th Biennial Convention, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 15)
- A New Member's Guide to the ACWA (Box 66, Folder 16)
- The Welfare Program of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Song Book (Box 66, Folder 18)
- The Clothing Workers in Philadelphia, 1940 (Box 66, Folder 19)
- John E. Williams: An Appreciation with Selections from His Writings (Box 66, Folder 20)
- 75th Anniversary Celebration Dinner, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 21)
- Records of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 22)
- The Story of a Bank, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 23)
- Celebrating the First Sixty Years (Box 66, Folder 24)
- 1991 Statement of Condition, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 25)
- We Face the Future: The Amalgamated Laundry Workers 35th Anniversary (Box 66, Folder 26)
- Scholarship Fund, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 27)
- The Jack Sheinkman Endowment Fund Dinner, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 28)
- Constitution, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 29)
- ACTWU and Civil Rights (Box 66, Folder 30)
- The ACTWU Song Book (Box 66, Folder 31)
- Constitution, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 32)
- A Commitment to Progress: The Dream Continues ACTWU 1972-1987 (Box 66, Folder 33)
- Fifth Constitutional Convention Program, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 34)
- Brand Name Directory of Products Made by ACTWU Members, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 35)
- ACTWU in Action: Report to the General Executive Board, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 36)
- ACTWU Conference: Sidney Hillman: From Chicago to National Leadership, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 37)
- News from the ACTWU: May 18, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 38)
- The Sidney Hillman Foundation: A Record of Service to the Community, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 39)
- Sidney Hillman Health Center (Box 66, Folder 40)
- Sidney Hillman 1887-1946, 1947 (Box 66, Folder 41)
- 40th Anniversary Luncheon, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 42)
- The First Five Years, 1946 (Box 66, Folder 43)
- The First Ten Years 1948-1957 (Box 66, Folder 44)
- Fifteen Year Report, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 45)
- Twenty Year Report 1948-1968 (Box 66, Folder 46)
- Sidney Hillman Health Centre and Chicago and Central States Joint Board, ACTWU, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 48)
- The Prize Award Program of the Sidney Hillman Foundation, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 49)
- The Prize Award Program for the Sidney Hillman Foundation, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 50)
- The Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc. Prize Award Luncheon, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 51)
- The Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc. at the Thirty-Fifth Anniversary of its Prize Awards, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 52)
- The Prize Award Program of the The Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc., 1985 (Box 66, Folder 52)
- The Prize Award Program of the Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc., 1986 (Box 66, Folder 53)
- The Prize Award Program of the Sidney Hillman Foundation, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 54)
- The Sidney Hillman Foundation at the Thirty-Eighth Anniversary of its Prize Awards, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 55)
- The Prize Award Program of the Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc., 1988 (Box 66, Folder 56)
- The Prize Award Program of the Sidney Hillman Foundation, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 57)
- The Prize Award Program of the Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc., 1990 (Box 66, Folder 58)
- The Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc. Prize Award Luncheon, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 59)
- The Prize Program of the Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc., 1992 (Box 66, Folder 60)
- The Prize Award of the Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc., 1993 (Box 66, Folder 61)
- The Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc. Prize Awards Luncheon, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 62)
- The Prize Award Program of the Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc., 1994 (Box 66, Folder 63)
- The Prize Program of the Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc., 1995 (Box 66, Folder 64)
- The Prize Award Program of the Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc., 1996 (Box 66, Folder 65)
- The Prize Award Program of the Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc., 1997 (Box 66, Folder 66)
- The Prize Award Program of the Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc., 1988 (Box 66, Folder 67)
- The Prize Award Program of the Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc., 1999 (Box 66, Folder 68)
- The Prize Award Program of the Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc., 2000 (Box 66, Folder 69)
- The Prize Award Program of the Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc., 2001 (Box 66, Folder 70)
- The Prize Award Program of the Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc., 2004 (Box 66, Folder 71)
- 55th Anniversary Celebration. The Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc. Awards Presentation, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 72)
- Moving Forward Together. June 30, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 73)
- Constitution and By-Laws, 1910 (Box 66, Folder 74)
- Political Action Manual '98, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 75)
- Manual de Accion Politica (Box 66, Folder 76)
- Union Health Center Report for the Year 1924 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Annual Report 1943 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Union Health Center ILGWU Philadelphia and Vicinity (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Medal for a Union: Fifty Years of the ILGWU Union Health Center (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Light and Illumination in Garment Shops, 1918 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Report for the Year 1926 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Reports: 1930, 1931 (bounded) (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Report for the Year 1934 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Report for 1922 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Report for Years 1935 and 1936, 1935-1936 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Interim Report 1944-1945 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Report for the Years 1941 and 1942 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Report for the Years 1922,1924,1926,1927 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Report for the Union Health Center Committee of the General Executive Board Meeting: March 6, 1957 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Report to the Union Health Center Committee of the ILGWU General Executive Board for the Year Ending December 31, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Report to the Union Health Center Committee of the ILGWU General Executive Board for the Year Ending December 31, 1971 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Report of the Union Health Center Committee of the ILGWU General Executive Board for the Year Ending December 31, 1972 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Report of the Union Health Center Committee of the ILGWU General Executive Board for the Year Ending December 31, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Report of the Union Health Center Committee of the ILGWU General Executive Board for the Year Ending December 31, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Report of the Union Health Center Committee of the ILGWU General Executive Board for the Year Ending December 31, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Union Health Center, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Report of the Union Health Center Committee of the ILGWU General Executive Board for the Year Ending December 31, 1983, 1984, 1985, 1990 and 1993, 1983-1993 (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Twenty First Anniversary of the Union Health Center, 1934 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Technical Report 1944-1946 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- The Health Department of Organized Labor, 1934 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Triennial Report 1947-1949 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Union Health Center News Vol.I, No.1, 1926 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Justice, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  v.48:no.19
- Justice, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  v.50. Assorted issues.
- Justice, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  v.51:no.2
- Justice, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  v.53:no.6
- Justice, 1974 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  v.56. Assorted issues.
- Justice, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  v.59. Assorted issues.
- Justice, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  v.60. Assorted issues.
- Justice, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  v.61. Assorted issues.
- Justice, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  v.62. Assorted issues.
- Justice, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  v.64. Assorted issues.
- Justice, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  v.65. Assorted issues.
- Justice, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  v.66
- Justice, 1985 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  v.67. Assorted issues.
- Justice, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  v.68. Assorted issues.
- Justice, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  v.69. Assorted issues.
- Justice, 1991 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  v.73:no.8
- Justice, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  v.74:no.5
- Justice, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  v.76:no.4
- Justicia Vol.LXV, No.5, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- ILGWU News-History 1900-1950 Golden Jubilee Convention (Box 69, Folder 1)
  May, 1950
- ILGWU News-History 1900-1950 Golden Jubilee Collection (Box 69, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Illustrated - 23rd Convention, 1937 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  May, 1937
- Scrap Book: The I.L.G.'er May 1956 - May 1959 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  May 11, 1959
- Union Breaking and Fake Unity: Cloakmakers Reply to Destructors and Dual Unionists (Box 69, Folder 4)
  English and Yiddish
- Union Breaking and Fake Unity: Cloakmakers Reply to Destructors and Dual Unionists (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Pins and Needles (Box 69, Folder 4)
  Presented by Labor Stage with the I.L.G.W.U. Players
- Pins and Needles (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Working People: The Art of Ralph Fasanella, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  Calendar
- Death Benefit Funds, 1950 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  Statement and Report: July 1, 1937 to December 31, 1949
- Picture of a Union…the ILGWU, 1959 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  May 17, 1959; Section 10
- "50th Anniversary Dance", 1983 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  List of event guests; sponsored by Local 155 Knitgoods Workers Union; October 22, 1983
- America's Largest Murals Show Unions Mean Progress in Garment Industry (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Konvenshon Kanarik, 1940 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  English and Yiddish; 40th Convention
- The Big Shot: Unconventional Organ of the Twenty-third Convention of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (Box 69, Folder 5)
  May 11, 1937
- The Big Shot: Unconventional Organ of the Twenty-third Convention of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (Box 69, Folder 5)
- The Big Shot: Unconventional Convention Journal of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (Box 69, Folder 5)
  June 1, 1940; Volume II, No. A-1
- The Little Big Shot: Unconventional Convention Appendix of the ILGWU (Box 69, Folder 5)
  June 8, 1940; Volume II No. B-4
- Delegates Guide: Big Shot Edition (Box 69, Folder 5)
  26th Convention - ILGWU
- The Big Shot: ILGWU Super-Kid Convention Edition (Box 69, Folder 5)
  June 3, 1944; Volume III, No. 4-F
- The Amalgamated Illustrated Almanac 1924 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Illustrated Almanac 1923, 1922 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Consumer Tips to Economy: Your Money's Worth, 1978 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- What They Wore: Highlights of Fashion History, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- A Policy Guide on Enforcing the Union Agreement (Box 70, Folder 3)
- ILGWU 1967 Staff Conference (Box 70, Folder 3)
  August 20 - August 22; David Gingold, Sol C. Chaikin; Louis Stulberg
- Our Aim (Box 70, Folder 3)
  1951-1954: Local 91, ILGWU
- To Promote the General Welfare: The Story of the Amalgamated, 1950 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Step by Step…1941-1966 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  A Report of 25 Years of Progress; Local 105; ILGWU; AFL-CIO
- Step by Step…1941-1966 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- 1910 Gerechtiekeit, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  Yiddish. Righteousness; September 1960; Special Jubilee Edition
- Your Job, Your Union and You (Box 70, Folder 5)
  Local 105 ILGWU
- The Tailor Re-Tailored: A Story of Surging Humanity 1910-1928 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  Amalgamated Centre; 1928 May Day
- The Picture That Came to Life… (Box 70, Folder 5)
  December 1951; The story of the Sidney Hillman Medical Center of the Male Apparel Industry of Philadelphia, and of the union which it serves
- The Goals We Share (Box 70, Folder 5)
  Local 105
- The Goals We Share (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Reporter, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  Trenton-Wilminton District; June-July, 1958; Vol. I
- Reporter, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  Trenton-Wilmington District; May 1958; Vol. I
- Reporter, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  Trenton-Wilmington District; September, 1958; Vol. I
- Reporter, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  Trenton-Wilmington District; March, 1959; Vol. II
- Reporter, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  Trenton-Wilmington District; January, 1959; Vol. II
- Reporter, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  Trenton-Wilmington District; December, 1958; Vol. I
- Reporter, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  Trenton-Wilmington District; November, 1958; Vol. I
- Reporter, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  Trenton-Wilmington District; October, 1958; Vol. I
- Union Messenger, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Vol. 1, No. 3; July, 1960
- Union Messenger, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Vol. 1, No. 5; December, 1960
- Union Messenger, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Vol. 2, No. 1; May, 1961
- Union Messenger, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Vol. 2, No. 2; December, 1961
- S.T.E.P. (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Volume 1, Number 3; December, 1969; bi-monthly publication; S.T.E.P. (Scholarship, Training, Education, Political)
- S.T.E.P., 1970 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Volume 1, Number 5; April, 1970; bi-monthly publication; S.T.E.P. (Scholarship, Training, Education, Political)
- S.T.E.P., 1970 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Volume 1, Number 6; Summer Edition; May-August, 1970; bi- monthly publication; S.T.E.P. (Scholarship, Training, Education, Political)
- S.T.E.P., 1970 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Volume 1, Number 7; September-October, 1970
- S.T.E.P., 1970 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Volume 1, Number 8; Winter Edition
- S.T.E.P., 1971 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Volume 3, Number 2; May-June, 1971; bi-monthly publication
- S.T.E.P., 1971 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Volume 3, Number 3; July-August, 1971; bi-monthly publication
- S.T.E.P., 1971 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Volume 3, Number 4; September-December, 1971; bi-monthly publication
- S.T.E.P., 1972 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Volume 3, Number 5; January-February, 1972; bi-monthly publication
- S.T.E.P., 1972 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Volume 3, Number 6; Spring-Summer 1972
- S.T.E.P., 1972 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Volume 3, Number 7; Fall-Winter, 1972; bi-monthly publication
- S.T.E.P., 1973 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Volume 4, Number 1; January - April 1973; bi-monthly publication
- S.T.E.P., 1973 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Volume 4, Number 2; May-June 1973; bi-monthly publication
- S.T.E.P., 1973 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Volume 4, Number 3; July-August 1973; bi-monthly publication
- S.T.E.P., 1973 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Volume 4, Number 4; Winter 1973-74; bi-monthly publication
- S.T.E.P., 1974 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Volume 5, Number 1; Summer, 1974; bi-monthly publication
- S.T.E.P., 1974 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Volume 5, Number 2; fall-Winter 1974; bi-monthly publication
- S.T.E.P., 1975 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Volume 5, Number 7; Jan.-Feb., 1975; bi-monthly publication
- 1933 - 1938 Fifth-Anniversary: South Jersey joint Board (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Convention hall Camden, N.J.; Oct 8th, 1938
- The I.L.G.'ER, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Vol. 20, No. 9; June, 1973
- Local 23-25 News, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  Volume 38, No. 2; April 1989
- The Chinatown Garment Industry Study: An Overview, 1983 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  June 15, 1983
- Politics Shapes Our Lives (Box 70, Folder 8)
- A Union Responds to Change (Box 70, Folder 8)
- The Thread of Life: Health and Welfare services (Box 70, Folder 8)
- The Thread of Life: Health and Welfare services, 1956 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- The Prosanis label (Box 70, Folder 8)
  Issued by The Joint Board of Sanitary Control; 31 Union Square; New York
- Shop Conditions: Skirt & Sportswear Industry (Box 70, Folder 8)
  Wages, hours, Overtime Pay, Holidays, Job Security; Local 23-25 ILGWU
- Shop Conditions (Box 70, Folder 8)
  Wages, Hours, Overtime Pay, Holidays, Job Security; Local 23-25 ILGWU
- On the Job Injury: Workers' compensation (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Unity House: A Workers' Shangri-La (Box 70, Folder 9)
- The Needlepoint, 1951 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 2; Issued by Wilkes-Barre - Pittston District Councils; July 1951
- The Needlepoint, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 40; January, 1958; Issued by Wilkes-Barre - Pittston - Nanticoke District Council
- The Needlepoint, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 41; February, 1958
- The Needlepoint, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 43; May 1958
- The Needlepoint (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 44; July, 1958
- The Needlepoint, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 45; September 1958
- The Needlepoint, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 46; December, 1958
- The Needlepoint, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 47; February, 1959
- The Needlepoint, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 48; April, 1959
- The Needlepoint, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 49; June, 1959
- The Needlepoint, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 50; August 1959
- The Needlepoint, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 51; October 1959
- The Needlepoint, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 52; December, 1959
- The Needlepoint, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 53; February, 1960
- The Needlepoint, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  number 54; April, 1960
- The Needlepoint, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 55; June, 1960
- The Needlepoint, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 56; August, 1960
- The Needlepoint, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 57; October 1960
- The Needlepoint, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 58; November, 1960
- The Needlepoint, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 59; February, 1961
- The Needlepoint, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 60; May, 1961
- The Needlepoint, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 61; August 1961
- The Needlepoint, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 62; January, 1962
- The Needlepoint, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 63; May, 1962
- The Needlepoint, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 64; September, 1962
- The Needlepoint, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- The Needlepoint, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 66; December, 1962
- The Needlepoint, 1963 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  Number 67; February, 1963
- JUSTICE: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  Vol. 54:no.14- 15; July 15-August 1, 1972
- Seamlines, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  Vol. 8, No. 1; June 20, 1962
- Seamlines, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  No. 1, Vol. 7; November, 1961
- Seamlines, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  No. 2, Vol. 5; April 1961
- Seamlines, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  No. 1, Vol. 5; June, 1961
- Seamlines, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  No.l 1, Vol. 5; January, 1961
- Seamlines, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  No. 7, Vol. 4; November 1960
- Seamlines, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  No. 7, Vol. 4; September, 1960
- Seamlines, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  No. 6, Vol. 4; May, 1960
- Seamlines, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  No. 5, Vol. 4; March, 1960
- Seamlines, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  No. 3, Vol. 4; October, 1959
- Seamlines, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  No. 3, Vol. 4; June, 1959
- Seamlines, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  No. 2, Vol. 4; April, 1959
- Seamlines, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  No. 1, Vol. 4; February, 1959
- The Chinatown Garment Industry Study, 1983 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  June, 1983
- A Comprehensive Approach to New York city Apparel manufacturing Development Policy (Box 70, Folder 12)
  March 1990
- A Study of Women's Apparel Buyers: Attitudes Toward Buying Trips to New York vs. Regional Markets, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 12)
- High Fashion High Tech High Skill: Notes on the Future of the American Apparel Industry (Box 70, Folder 12)
- The People Speak: Letters from Clothing Workers, 1940 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  Prize Winners in a "WRITE-A-LETTER-FOR-ROOSEVELT" Contest; Sponsored by the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, October, 1940
- The Impact of the 42nd Street Redevelopment Project on the Garment Industry, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  October, 1984
- Los Angeles Jewish Commission on Sweatshops, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  January 1999
- new York City Garment Center Study; Program and Zoning Recommendations, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  October, 1986
- New York City Garment Center Study: Program and Zoning Recommendations, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 15)
- Garment Center Enforcement Project, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  Report for May 1, 1989 through July 31, 1989; Quarterly Report
- Geographic Atlas of Industrial, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  1991 Update; Follow-up to the Citywide Industry Study; March 1994
- The Chinatown Garment Industry Study, 1983 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  Submitted to Local 23-25 ILGWU and the New York Skirt and Sportswear Association; June, 1983
- Agreement (Box 70, Folder 18)
  1961-1964
- At Your Service: The Story of Your Union's Welfare Program and You (Box 70, Folder 18)
- Manual for Shop Representatives (Box 70, Folder 18)
- Manual for Shop Representatives (Box 70, Folder 18)
  3rd edition
- How to Protect your Rights, 1957 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  September 1957
- New Gains New Goals (Box 70, Folder 18)
- Service tells the Story…, 1951 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  Local 105 ILGWU Tenth Anniversary 1941-1951
- New Members Kit (Box 70, Folder 18)
- A Good Union Never Rests (Box 70, Folder 18)